<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: event | Kelvin Li]]></title>
  <link href="http://memodir.github.com/blog/categories/event/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://memodir.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-10-06T00:29:00+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://memodir.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Kelvin Li]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[kelvin@memodir.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[startup of memodir]]></title>
    <link href="http://memodir.github.com/blog/2012/10/04/startup-of-memodir-blog/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-04T23:07:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://memodir.github.com/blog/2012/10/04/startup-of-memodir-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2><strong>MemoDir</strong></h2>

<p><img src="https://jeevmw.bay.livefilestore.com/y1pmaJRDhVNAk3OU7j3O5l478sGmn5LtePNkHoRiJhpN5XJVdyh9JeowS6WhSY_7mthQxYMmMYVJBk-S9_NTmtAlb9qFcJRTSDU/sunrise2.jpg" title="Sunrise on Huang mountain" alt="sunrise" /></p>

<h2>What is MemoDir?</h2>

<blockquote><p><strong>MemoDir</strong>, is a service for people to memorize their most important moments, things and persons in his/her life and share those exciting memoeries with friends.  <br/>
The only thing we care about is your <span style='color:blue'><strong>cherish memory</strong></span>.</p></blockquote>

<h2>How does the idea come from?</h2>

<p>Now most of people lives in a busy but wonderful world, things happened every day, good or bad, happy or sad… Those memory should have different colors at that moment. With the time goes by, it is getting fade in, but the color itself is supposed to be stay.</p>

<p>In you life, you have this responsibility to record some of your most important seconds, no matter with the photo, video or text, you should cherish that, for yourself or for your close family.</p>

<p>That's where the memodir came from. I hope each moment can be frozed with the color in some place, and some day, we can go there and release yourself from the this moement and memorize that moment. Green, Blue or Red, happiness, modness or excitement.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Why this name?</h2>

<p>You pieces of memories stay in the different directories.  Each directory owns its special style.</p>

<h2>Any meaning for this blog?</h2>

<p>The application is under the development as a startup. During this exciting period, a lot of startup affairs happen, the technical problem, programming bugs, site hosting, marketing decision.</p>

<p>This site tracks all of the activities on the memodir.
As the first artical in the blog, I wish in the soon future, the users can see this growing blog of the product.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
